{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869573124","data":{"timestamp":" 946869573124"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869574087","data":{"timestamp":" 946869574087"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869576997","data":{"timestamp":" 946869576997"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869577530","data":{"timestamp":" 946869577530"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869578172","data":{"timestamp":" 946869578172"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869582283","data":{"timestamp":" 946869582283"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869583206","data":{"timestamp":" 946869583206"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869586808","data":{"timestamp":" 946869586808"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869587590","data":{"timestamp":" 946869587590"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869588564","data":{"timestamp":" 946869588563"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869592430","data":{"timestamp":" 946869592430"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869593394","data":{"timestamp":" 946869593394"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869596314","data":{"timestamp":" 946869596314"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869596847","data":{"timestamp":" 946869596847"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869597491","data":{"timestamp":" 946869597491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869601575","data":{"timestamp":" 946869601574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869602497","data":{"timestamp":" 946869602497"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869606093","data":{"timestamp":" 946869606092"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869606876","data":{"timestamp":" 946869606875"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869607848","data":{"timestamp":" 946869607848"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869611124","data":{"timestamp":" 946869611123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869611215","data":{"timestamp":" 946869611215"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7a252650-3ee2-4f82-84b1-14efb49be375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869634597","data":{"timestamp":" 946869634597"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869658418","data":{"timestamp":" 946869658418"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869676258","data":{"timestamp":" 946869676258"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869712000","data":{"timestamp":" 946869712000"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869728609","data":{"timestamp":" 946869728609"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869806460","data":{"timestamp":" 946869806460"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869830761","data":{"timestamp":" 946869830761"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869876926","data":{"timestamp":" 946869876926"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869904293","data":{"timestamp":" 946869904293"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869926284","data":{"timestamp":" 946869926284"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869935982","data":{"timestamp":" 946869935982"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869942629","data":{"timestamp":" 946869942628"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869947856","data":{"timestamp":" 946869947856"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869973970","data":{"timestamp":" 946869973970"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869978800","data":{"timestamp":" 946869978799"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869984901","data":{"timestamp":" 946869984901"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869991392","data":{"timestamp":" 946869991392"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" f98e8b84-5550-4819-ae4a-83bbc3c81275"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870005082","data":{"timestamp":" 946870005082"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870074800","data":{"timestamp":" 946870074800"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870121274","data":{"timestamp":" 946870121274"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870143078","data":{"timestamp":" 946870143077"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870154512","data":{"timestamp":" 946870154512"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870186638","data":{"timestamp":" 946870186638"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870196576","data":{"timestamp":" 946870196576"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870210222","data":{"timestamp":" 946870210222"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870227863","data":{"timestamp":" 946870227862"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870246209","data":{"timestamp":" 946870246209"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870253700","data":{"timestamp":" 946870253700"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870259194","data":{"timestamp":" 946870259194"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870264295","data":{"timestamp":" 946870264295"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870269498","data":{"timestamp":" 946870269498"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0826c679-8a1a-4c1f-b68f-d7f583830b0e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870283464","data":{"timestamp":" 946870283464"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870295577","data":{"timestamp":" 946870295577"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870315201","data":{"timestamp":" 946870315201"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_383_832-998-383"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 383"," userResponse":" 383"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870339191","data":{"timestamp":" 946870339191"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870350429","data":{"timestamp":" 946870350428"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870364714","data":{"timestamp":" 946870364714"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870383624","data":{"timestamp":" 946870383624"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_625_625-379-224"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 625"," userResponse":" 625"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870399391","data":{"timestamp":" 946870399391"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870415850","data":{"timestamp":" 946870415850"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 422"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870432976","data":{"timestamp":" 946870432975"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870442482","data":{"timestamp":" 946870442482"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870447167","data":{"timestamp":" 946870447167"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870453848","data":{"timestamp":" 946870453848"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870459060","data":{"timestamp":" 946870459060"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870472945","data":{"timestamp":" 946870472945"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 7960bfb7-4afa-4aba-9fca-858a0ad48e0f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870487481","data":{"timestamp":" 946870487481"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 16ae0115-df2f-4cae-a9b2-1fffc84e2536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870490356","data":{"timestamp":" 946870490356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 16ae0115-df2f-4cae-a9b2-1fffc84e2536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870490579","data":{"timestamp":" 946870490579"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 16ae0115-df2f-4cae-a9b2-1fffc84e2536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870496510","data":{"timestamp":" 946870496510"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 16ae0115-df2f-4cae-a9b2-1fffc84e2536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870503573","data":{"timestamp":" 946870503573"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 16ae0115-df2f-4cae-a9b2-1fffc84e2536"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870512220","data":{"timestamp":" 946870512220"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0b72e788-ac4f-4b34-8002-04faac7fe57e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 885"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870629981","data":{"timestamp":" 946870629981"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870631657","data":{"timestamp":" 946870631656"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870642365","data":{"timestamp":" 946870642365"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870648130","data":{"timestamp":" 946870648130"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870664575","data":{"timestamp":" 946870664575"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870684156","data":{"timestamp":" 946870684156"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870689973","data":{"timestamp":" 946870689973"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 0d6e73ab-a592-4ea4-a5b8-6e03f1ec4681"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870699462","data":{"timestamp":" 946870699462"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870699686","data":{"timestamp":" 946870699686"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870700594","data":{"timestamp":" 946870700594"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870700690","data":{"timestamp":" 946870700690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870706436","data":{"timestamp":" 946870706436"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870729359","data":{"timestamp":" 946870729359"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870734753","data":{"timestamp":" 946870734753"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870741640","data":{"timestamp":" 946870741640"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870747472","data":{"timestamp":" 946870747472"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870755428","data":{"timestamp":" 946870755428"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870762864","data":{"timestamp":" 946870762863"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870769930","data":{"timestamp":" 946870769929"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 75e37849-5b37-4ed6-aa4c-b9f06deb7510"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870780174","data":{"timestamp":" 946870780174"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870781843","data":{"timestamp":" 946870781843"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870787453","data":{"timestamp":" 946870787452"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870795512","data":{"timestamp":" 946870795512"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870795518","data":{"timestamp":" 946870795518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870795524","data":{"timestamp":" 946870795523"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" KIANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870796543","data":{"timestamp":" 946870796543"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870804815","data":{"timestamp":" 946870804814"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870817181","data":{"timestamp":" 946870817181"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870818642","data":{"timestamp":" 946870818642"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870825963","data":{"timestamp":" 946870825963"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870828446","data":{"timestamp":" 946870828446"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870830690","data":{"timestamp":" 946870830690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870832513","data":{"timestamp":" 946870832513"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870835160","data":{"timestamp":" 946870835160"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870838403","data":{"timestamp":" 946870838403"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870847911","data":{"timestamp":" 946870847911"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870849809","data":{"timestamp":" 946870849809"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870852212","data":{"timestamp":" 946870852212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870854757","data":{"timestamp":" 946870854757"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870857755","data":{"timestamp":" 946870857755"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870859439","data":{"timestamp":" 946870859439"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870861446","data":{"timestamp":" 946870861446"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870865210","data":{"timestamp":" 946870865210"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870867190","data":{"timestamp":" 946870867189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870869457","data":{"timestamp":" 946870869456"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870871609","data":{"timestamp":" 946870871609"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870874606","data":{"timestamp":" 946870874606"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870876585","data":{"timestamp":" 946870876585"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870878692","data":{"timestamp":" 946870878692"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870880675","data":{"timestamp":" 946870880675"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870882265","data":{"timestamp":" 946870882265"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870884407","data":{"timestamp":" 946870884407"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870886591","data":{"timestamp":" 946870886591"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870889246","data":{"timestamp":" 946870889246"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870891544","data":{"timestamp":" 946870891544"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870894356","data":{"timestamp":" 946870894356"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870896565","data":{"timestamp":" 946870896565"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870899348","data":{"timestamp":" 946870899348"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870901341","data":{"timestamp":" 946870901341"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870903769","data":{"timestamp":" 946870903769"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870906032","data":{"timestamp":" 946870906031"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870907748","data":{"timestamp":" 946870907748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870909757","data":{"timestamp":" 946870909757"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870911710","data":{"timestamp":" 946870911710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870913577","data":{"timestamp":" 946870913577"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOYAONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870915664","data":{"timestamp":" 946870915664"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870920738","data":{"timestamp":" 946870920738"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870920955","data":{"timestamp":" 946870920955"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870920959","data":{"timestamp":" 946870920959"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" BUIBUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870923400","data":{"timestamp":" 946870923400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" ANANSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870926645","data":{"timestamp":" 946870926645"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870927761","data":{"timestamp":" 946870927761"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870929776","data":{"timestamp":" 946870929776"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870932527","data":{"timestamp":" 946870932527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870932532","data":{"timestamp":" 946870932532"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870942408","data":{"timestamp":" 946870942408"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870944857","data":{"timestamp":" 946870944857"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870952835","data":{"timestamp":" 946870952835"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870955142","data":{"timestamp":" 946870955141"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870957191","data":{"timestamp":" 946870957190"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870958960","data":{"timestamp":" 946870958960"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870961137","data":{"timestamp":" 946870961137"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870963178","data":{"timestamp":" 946870963178"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870965124","data":{"timestamp":" 946870965124"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870967804","data":{"timestamp":" 946870967804"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870970555","data":{"timestamp":" 946870970555"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870972955","data":{"timestamp":" 946870972955"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870973588","data":{"timestamp":" 946870973588"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870973850","data":{"timestamp":" 946870973850"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946870992622","data":{"timestamp":" 946870992622"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871001184","data":{"timestamp":" 946871001184"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 990e1816-e5b5-4839-a5df-cd7f44ea2de6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871011411","data":{"timestamp":" 946871011410"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871011639","data":{"timestamp":" 946871011638"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871012607","data":{"timestamp":" 946871012607"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871013894","data":{"timestamp":" 946871013893"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871016930","data":{"timestamp":" 946871016930"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871017781","data":{"timestamp":" 946871017780"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871018094","data":{"timestamp":" 946871018094"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871019328","data":{"timestamp":" 946871019328"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871022824","data":{"timestamp":" 946871022824"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871023808","data":{"timestamp":" 946871023808"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871024064","data":{"timestamp":" 946871024064"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871025016","data":{"timestamp":" 946871025015"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871027907","data":{"timestamp":" 946871027906"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871028941","data":{"timestamp":" 946871028940"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871029413","data":{"timestamp":" 946871029413"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871033983","data":{"timestamp":" 946871033981"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871034080","data":{"timestamp":" 946871034080"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871040626","data":{"timestamp":" 946871040626"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_061913"," gameId":" 90961a36-d65b-478a-a3df-127800822551"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}